I am getting a little older I'm not old
but I'm in my 30s is anyone in that age
range here yeah wow you're pretty happy
about it that's good
good job usually they're like yeah here
it's funny because for some reason the
second you turn 30 you start saying
you're old you're like that's it I'm old
now
I'm old and then for 10 years you just
keep saying it you're like I'm old I'm
old I'm old I'm old and then you turn 40
and you're like now I'm old I could have
been young for an extra 10 years but I
wasted it saying I was old now I've lost
10 extra years where he could have been
young then you turn 80 you're like now
I'm really old I could have been just
kind of old now I'm really old then you
die and you're like I could have been
alive for 82 and a half years now I'm
dead I can't even have this brilliant
thought so my point is none of us are
old because we're still here
yeah still doing it who's in their 20s
anybody all right yeah you're you're
happier that's good twenty twenties I
don't relate to it's like it's a good
time but I don't relate to it anymore
because I'm like you guys are so cute
because you still think you matter
like the rest your life is just this
really long journey where you'll find
out you matter less and last and less
every day and then you die not to give
it away but that's
what you can look forward to I feel like
you spend your twenties sort of waiting
for your life to start you know you guys
look so young are you how old are you 20
exactly
he's just so ready for it to start
already right and that's how it is
you're like next year I'm gonna I'm
gonna get that big job and my life is
gonna start and then another year goes
by you're like next year I'm gonna fall
madly in love and my life is gonna start
then another year goes by and you're
like next year I'm gonna get two towels
and my life is gonna start and then you
turn 30 and you're like it started this
is my life like waiting for the bus to
come you're already on the bus you're
like wins the bus getting here and
they're like you are on it you are on
the bus you're like why am i riding a
bus
[Music]
there's activities that I want to do as
much in my 30s like I went to a bar
recently with my friend and we lasted
like five minutes and got bored we're
like you want to go yeah let's let's go
and as we're walking our cars my friends
like oh my god Erica we're getting older
we're not fun anymore no no no that's
not what's happening okay it's not that
we're not fun anymore it's oh we're
getting older and we're getting smarter
and we're starting to realize it was
never fun we just pretended this whole
time
hey did you know Drybar comedy has its
own app download it now to watch my
whole special